{
    "id": "d2c6154db3024bb5b9838d7af807a8d1",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What she said ………………………. not true.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody …………………….. there to help him.",
            "description": "Nobody is followed by a singular verb.",
            "answers": [
                "were",
                "was",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody called, …………………………..?",
            "description": "Nobody is a negative word hence, it is followed by an affirmative tag. ",
            "answers": [
                "didn't they",
                "did they",
                "had they"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone of them ………………………….. arrived.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after every and everyone. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ………………………….. not the right thing to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "certain",
                "certainly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. you did cannot be justified.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "What",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The thing …………………………… happened next shocked us.",
            "description": "As a relative pronoun that can refer to things. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "that which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………………. to the market. He should be here soon.",
            "description": "The present perfect is used here because he is still in the market. ",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "has gone",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The milkman has already …………………………..",
            "description": "Has been is used to talk about a finished action. The milkman has already been means the milkman came and went. ",
            "answers": [
                "been",
                "come"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Jack London is regarded ………………………….. one of the best American novelists.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Considered ………………………….. a whole, the movie wasn’t bad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Clever …………………………. she was, she couldn’t solve the puzzle.",
            "description": "Clever as she was and clever though she was both mean 'though she was clever'.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}